haacked.com 2008-06-23

# Privacy Policy

**What? Why Have A Privacy Policy?**  
Well, you wouldn't want Haacked.com sharing all sorts of deeply personal information about you, would you? Well of course not. Besides, some affiliate programs require a privacy policy. So here you go, a privacy policy.

**Besides Your Rear, What Does The Policy Cover?**   
This privacy policy covers how Haacked.com treats personal information it receives from visitors. It gives the average reader the assurance that his or her personal information is safe from Big Brother and other prying eyes. 

**How Do You Guarantee Privacy?**  
As in life, there are no perfect guarantees. However, as Haacked.com doesn't require registration, it really doesn't have much information to share in the first place. 

**What Information Do You Collect?**  
That's just it, there's hardly any information to collect. About the only personal information this site may have about you is anything you disclose within the comments section of the site or via the Contact Us page. Regarding the comments, that information is publicly available as it is displayed on the site. If you don't want it displayed, don't comment. Or make up false information. Haacked.com has no way of knowing. 

**What About Cookies?**  
Haacked.com automatically receives and records information in its server logs from your browser, including your IP Address, cookie information (should you request to be remembered), and the page you request. This information is used to generate aggregate statistics such as the # of users, visits, etc... This is a function of the blogging engine (Subtext).

**So Who Do You Share This Information With?**  
Absolutely nobody. 

**Even If I Offered You 10 Million Dollars?**  
Let's talk off-line in private.... er... I mean NO! Absolutely Not. Haacked.com doesn't gather any information worth selling. 

[ad] [Free Bug Tracking & Project Management Software](http://www.axosoft.com/?gad=CNrd-I4DEgh-LBK3JraEchjw16__AyD6s9Er "Sponsored Message") Axosoft’s OnTime 2007 allows software development teams to collaborate on software projects by tracking everything from defects to enhancements to helpdesk incidents in one easy-to-use database driven by an intuitive Windows, Web or VS.NET Integrated UI. **[Get a Free Single-User License](http://www.axosoft.com/?gad=CNrd-I4DEgh-LBK3JraEchjw16__AyD6s9Er "License")** ($200 Value!)
